https://www.lurie-zepeda.com/privacy-policy/

Overview
Your use of our web site is subject to this privacy policy and the web site Terms of Use. By using our web site, you are accepting the practices set out in this privacy policy and our terms and conditions of use. This privacy policy applies to Lurie, Zepeda, Schmalz, Hogan & Martin and it does not apply to other companies’ or organizations’ web sites to which our web site may link. You should carefully review the privacy policies of those web sites in order to determine how they treat your personally identifiable information.
Information Gathered From Visitors
If you use our web site to simply learn about our firm and the services we offer, we may gather certain generic information with respect to your use of our web site, including, the frequency and length of your visit, the areas on our web site that you viewed, and your IP address. We only use this generic information to help identify areas of interest on our web site and to customize and improve our web site in order to make your experience easier and more enjoyable.
We may use a technology nicknamed “cookies” on our web site. Cookies are pieces of information or data sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies may be set upon your browser during site visits to save your site customization preferences. Cookies help you navigate our web site, and help us customize our web site to provide personal service.
If you provide us with personally identifiable information by or through your use of our web site or through a separate e-mail to one of our attorneys or staff members, including your name, home or e-mail address, telephone number, or any other information that permits us to contact you, we may use such personally identifiable information to contact you and to send you other information concerning Lurie, Zepeda, Schmalz, Hogan & Martin.
Disclosure and Exceptions
We do not sell or share any of your personally identifiable information with or to any third parties, provided that we may disclose your personally identifiable information to appropriate third parties if we are required to do so by law or with your prior consent.
Other Matters
If you do not want us to continue to use information that you have previously provided to us on or through our web site, or if you wish to make corrections or changes to information that you have previously provided, please contact our office manager at 310-274-8700.
We do not knowingly collect, maintain, or use personally identifiable information from anyone under 18 years of age, and our web site is not structured to attract anyone under 13 years of age. In addition, California law permits visitors to web sites who are residents of California to request information regarding the web site owner’s disclosure of their personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. It is our policy not to disclose your personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes.
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time by posting the changes on this page. If there is a material change in our privacy policy, we will indicate on our web site that our policy has changed and provide a link to the new/revised privacy statement. Please check the effective date below to determine if the policy has been modified since you last reviewed it. Your continued use of any portion of our web site following posting of the updated privacy policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.
December 1, 2014
Search for:
Your Case.
Our Strategy.
Problem Solved.
Latest News
December 4, 2020
OUR CENTURY CITY OFFICE IS NOW OPEN FOR BUSINESS (With Face Masks and Plenty of Hand Sanitizer and Social Distancing)
September 2, 2020
Steve Hogan and Damien Holcomb obtain an eight figure settlement in Will Contest in San Bernardino
March 10, 2020
Steve Hogan and Kurt Schmalz Selected As Super Lawyers For 2020
April 22, 2019
Troy Martin Awarded Presidential Volunteer Service Award for Work Fighting Elder Abuse
February 2, 2019
Steve Hogan and Kurt Schmalz Selected As Super Lawyers For 2019
Browse More News
“When a trusted employee embezzled from me and stole trade secrets, Troy Martin kept me sane.  He is patient, kind and very knowledgeable.  Troy’s exceptionally clear lawsuit was so easy for the jury to follow that we won the case with a seven figure verdict.”
“I experienced a surprisingly positive outcome from very a complex estate situation.    All my concerns were addressed.    Resolving our communication challenges were accomplished while navigating a California case from my home in New Mexico.”
“It is important for us to work with down-to-earth, honest, respectful attorneys.  The attorneys at Lurie, Zepeda, Schmalz, Hogan & Martin are all of those things and more.”
“When my trust and estate planning clients need a litigator, I refer them Lurie, Zepeda, Schmalz, Hogan & Martin.  The attorneys are experienced, focused and personable, and reduce my clients’ stress levels.  Also, the staff is polite and the environment is highly professional.”
“Steve Hogan and I have shared a nice reciprocal relationship for over 10 years.  He is everything you want in a litigator – innovative, smart, personable and relentless.”
“I originally met Steve Hogan when we were opposing counsel.  We developed a trusting relationship and I confidently refer clients with trusts and estate disputes to Steve.”
“I was unsure about pursuing litigation to resolve a long-standing dispute with family members over property.  Steve Hogan made me comfortable with the decision to move forward, and we won our case.  Steve is very personable and was in-tune with the many issues I was facing throughout the process.”
“I gained a lot of confidence in Troy Martin from co-litigating a case with him.  He is easy to work with and has a great demeanor for handling trust, estate and probate litigation.”
“I confidently refer Trust and Estate litigation matters to Steve Hogan for his specific experience in this area.  He skillfully pursues the desired outcome, overcoming the challenge of difficult opponents, is timely, and a great communicator.”
“Resolving a complex trust and estate litigation in California from our home in London was challenging.  Retaining Steve Hogan to represent us based on a friend’s strong recommendation turned out to be the right decision.”
“I seriously like Steve Hogan and refer clients who have Trust and Estate litigation issues to him.  Steve gets great results and has a reasonable approach to meeting with clients and billing.”
“I call Kurt Schmalz when one of my clients is facing litigation in California.  Since he tries a lot of cases, he knows the judges, unique characteristics of various jurisdictions, and the art of picking a jury.  He leverages these skills to settle cases when possible, and always is prepared to go to trial if needed.”
“Steve Hogan is my go-to choice when a client needs a Trusts and Estates litigator.  He does a tremendous job representing clients and keeps me informed throughout the process.”
"The Hogan-Holcomb team of Lurie, Zepeda, Schmalz, Hogan & Martin, A.P.C.  stuck with me through a hard-fought 3-year case involving a very complicated estate with a myriad of twists and turns unimaginable!   They got it to a settlement where my Life Concerns were more-than met enabling me a future lifetime of security and prosperity.   The many twists and turns were met with their immediate knowledge, instinct and creativity resulting in a true success!   They stuck with me through thick and thin and I'd recommend them to anyone dealing with an estate matter where winning matters!   I was up against a very well-manned team and I called-in the BEST!   Needless to say using Steve Hogan and Damien Holcomb was one of the wisest choices in my life!"
“Whenever my firm has a conflict, I confidently refer clients to Steve Hogan because he cares as much about them as I do.  He is very tenacious and gets great results.   Practicing law is not just a job for Steve, it is his passion.”
“I have spent a lot of time working side-by-side with Lurie, Zepeda, Schmalz, Hogan & Martin’s attorneys as an expert witness for their cases.   They are fantastic litigators, hardworking and fun to be around.”
“Over the years, I’ve used a lot of lawyers for different matters.  I like Lurie, Zepeda, Schmalz, Hogan & Martin’s high quality service.  They are quick and professional and provide excellent value for their rates.
“The partners and associates at Lurie, Zepeda, Schmalz, Hogan & Martin are amazing attorneys and very down-to-earth.   They patiently kept me informed of my options in fighting an employee’s wrongful termination case, and we got a great outcome.”
“Troy Martin has successfully resolved real estate and trust litigation for my clients.  He is very responsive and strategically considers potential outcomes versus potential costs when planning the best path to pursue.”
“I quickly gained confidence in Troy Martin.  He listens carefully, is rational in his approach, and thoughtfully explains the calculations behind his communications with the opposing side.  Troy achieved our desired outcome by patiently negotiating a settlement, saving us a lot of money in the long run.”
“Kurt Schmalz is a wonderful lawyer.  He is meticulous in his legal work and applied his outstanding abilities to win our civil case, write the appeal and then give an extraordinary argument before the court.”
“When I need co-counsel in California, I call Kurt Schmalz.  He is smart, knowledgeable and very experienced trying cases in the local courts, which is of great value to me and my clients.  Kurt takes the time to understand a case and provides insightful input during every step of the process.”
“Extremely valuable real estate divided our family after my father passed away.  I needed the best attorney in town, and fortunately was referred to Troy Martin.  Troy took a personal interest in my case and patiently pursued a successful settlement strategy rather than high-billing litigation.”
“Troy Martin is a very diligent attorney.   Probate litigation is a complicated process and Troy does a good job of explaining things to my clients, making it much easier for me.”
“Kurt Schmalz is one of the best litigators in Southern California.  He is intelligent, careful, results-oriented, and practical in his approach.  Kurt is a phenomenal choice for any client.”
“The Hogan team were dedicated, informed, all the while encouraging positive forward thinking to ensure the best outcome on my behalf.  Steve offered up his associate attorney to work closely with us while also keeping our litigation fees to a minimum.   The entire firm treated me as I were family.”
Website Designed and Built by Elimint
| Log in
